http://endometriosis.org/about/privacy-policy/

RSS FEEDNewsResourcesAbout endometriosisTreatmentsSupportGlossaryFAQsCongress schedule Search
Find Privacy policyEndometriosis.org maintains a strict privacy policy.Endometriosis.org does not share, nor sell, the names or contact details of those, who register with us or those who contact us.When you register with Endometriosis.org to receive regular emails about news in endometriosis we store your contact details securely. When you receive an email from Endometriosis.org you always have the option to unsubscribe at any time.Endometriosis.org displays Google ads and Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site (these ads enable us to provide this free service). Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. You, as a user, has the option to opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.By using this website you accept the use of cookies.Please also read the disclaimer.
Stay up to dateRegister for endometriosis news: Email Address
About usThe teamPeer review boardPrivacy policyAdvertising policyNotice of copyrightDisclaimer
Connect
Follow us on Twitter
Connect to the endometriosis community on FacebookGet involvedHelp us improve treatments for endometriosis and prevent this disease in the next generation of women. Support the work of the World Endometriosis Research Foundation. Donate to research Shop for WERF Volunteer
NewsResourcesAbout endometriosisAbout usSitemapTreatmentsSupportGlossaryFAQsCongress scheduleRSSThis site is peer-reviewed for accuracysite by culturegraphic© 2005-2020 endometriosis.orgDisclaimerPrivacy PolicyPage Last Updated: 23 May 2018
